(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-18T03:12:59.800466",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Grimoire 4 Ever 〜四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書〜
[Title: Grimoire 4 Ever - A Grimoire Written by Four, Remaining for Eternity]
君に届け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars reach you
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Tightly packing all these feelings inside
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony we create with you
これからもずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever and ever
ねぇねぇ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, come closer to us
回り始めた世界で踊らない？ 終わらない
Won't you dance in this spinning world? It never ends
わくわく 魔法かけたら
When we cast an exciting spell
ドキドキは Syncして ほら Party Time 止まらない
Our hearts sync together; look, the party time won't stop
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Put your wishes into them
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で歌いましょう
Let's sing in the night sky
君に響け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars resound to you
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と繋がっている この宇宙に
In this cosmos connected with you
宝石を散りばめよう
Let's scatter jewels across it
君に届け 星のメロディー
May the melody of the stars reach you
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Tightly packing all these feelings inside
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony we create with you
これからもずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever and ever
Clap Clap ほら 一緒に鳴らそう
Clap, clap, come on, let's clap together
この瞬間をキャッチして 忘れない Starry Night
Catch this moment—an unforgettable starry night
キラキラ 魔法解けても
Even if the sparkling magic fades away
胸にしまったトキメキは 消えない 止まらない
The excitement in our hearts won't fade or stop
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Put your wishes into them
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で踊りましょう
Let's dance in the night sky
Twinkle 4 You
Twinkle for you
君と残す 星のメモリー
Leaving behind memories of stars with you
思い出 ギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Tightly packing all our memories inside
君と会えた この素敵な奇跡と夢を
This wonderful miracle of meeting you and our dreams
奇跡と夢を
...miracles and dreams...
また叶えよう
Let's make them come true again.
君に響け 星のメロディー
Echo to you, melody of stars!
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation...
君と繋がっているこの宇宙に
In this universe connecting me with you,
宝石を散りばめよう
let's scatter jewels!
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach you, melody of stars!
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing our feelings tight,
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
this harmony we play with you...
これからもずっと続いてく
will continue forever on.
La La La...
La La La La...
イエーイ！
Yeah!
お待たせいたしました！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
配信でご覧の皆さん ねぽらぼ6周年記念ライブGrimoire Foreverへお越しいただきありがとうございます！
To everyone watching, welcome to NePoLaBo's 6th Anniversary 3D Live "Grimoire Forever"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
はい 私達ねぽらぼでーす！
Yes, we are NePoLaBo!
というわけで簡単な挨拶 自己紹介 ねねからどうぞ！
Let's do quick self-introductions, starting with Nene!
はい！ホロライブ5期生 オレンジの魔法 ピンクの桃汁 みんなのエナジードリンク 桃鈴ねねでーす！
Hi! Hololive 5th Gen, orange magic, pink peach juice, everyone's energy drink, Momosuzu Nene here!
はーい ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい ポルカです！ポルカおるか？おるよー！赤色の魔法...であってるのかな？はい ポルカです！よろしくお願いします！
Hi, Polka here! Is Polka here? Here I am! Red magic... is that right? Yep, I'm Polka! Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
はい！ホロライブの肝臓 雪花ラミィです！青色の魔法です！よろしくお願いします！
Hi! Hololive's liver, Yukihana Lamy here! Blue magic! Nice to meet you!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
はい じゃあねぽらぼの黒魔導士 獅白ぼたんです！
Alright, I'm NePoLaBo's dark mage, Shishiro Botan!
黒魔導士！かっこいい！この世のすべてを滅ぼす...
Dark mage! So cool! Destroying everything in this world...
今回のですね 配信のハッシュタグはこちら！
The hashtag for today's stream is right here!
ハッシュタグ #ねぽらぼ6周年3Dライブ こちらでお願いしまーす！
Hashtag #NePoLaBo6thAnniversary3DLive, please use this!
皆さん たくさんポストしてください！ラミィたちもチェックします！
Everyone, please post a lot! We'll be checking them too!
流しましょう！目指せ1位！
Let's flood the feed! Aiming for #1!
そして いよいよ周年ライブ始まりましたけど どうですか皆さん？
And now our anniversary live has finally started! How is everyone feeling?
いや ワクワクドキドキ！今回のライブコンセプトを説明していただけますか？
Man, super excited! Could someone explain today's live concept?
今回のコンセプトはね 「8月の魔法」！キャッチコピーは「4人で綴られ 永遠に残る 魔導書」！魔法少女をイメージとした帽子とステッキ！
Today's concept is "August Magic"! The slogan is "A grimoire written by four, remaining forever"! Hats and wands themed after magical girls!
ステキ！ステキだね！こちらを特別に作っていただきました！
Lovely! So lovely! These were specially made for us!
そうですね そのコンセプトに合うステージも作っていただきました！
That's right, and they also made a stage that fits this concept!
すごーい！壮大！これうち浮いてる？宇宙？星空に囲まれたステージで今日はライブをするんだね！
Awesome! So grand! Are we floating? In space? So we're performing on a stage surrounded by starry skies!
そういうことに！すごーい！
That's right! Amazing!
あ 見てこれ！専用の足元！
Ah, look at this! Special floor markings!
ねねさんあっちやん！これ専用魔法陣！すごい！
Nene-san, yours is over there! These are custom magic circles! Incredible!
ライブでいっぱい見せていきたいね！
We want to show them off a lot during the live!
まあそんな中でね 1曲目からみんなでちょっと魔法とかもこうかけまくっちゃったわけですけれども どうでしたか魔法？
Well, amidst all this, we've been casting all sorts of magic right from the first song, so how was the magic?
魔法かけてた！えーっとまず1曲目『Twinkle 4 You』をGrimoire Remixということで 新しくリミックスしていただきました！ちょっと違ったでしょ いつもと？
We were casting magic! First off, the 1st song "Twinkle 4 You" was remixed as the Grimoire Remix! It was a bit different from usual, right?
ちょっと違ったよね！ちょっとタイミング難しいとこあるんだよね！あそこ難しかったけど...
Yeah, it was a bit different! The timing was a bit tricky in places! That part was tough, but...
まあなんとか今日も頑張りましたね 皆さん！頑張りました！
Well, we somehow did our best today, everyone! We did our best!
で そこで魔導書に魔法で映像投影したり あと歌詞もさ この上の方に出したりしてもらいました！
And we had videos projected onto the grimoire with magic, and lyrics displayed up above too!
ね！この空間に魔法に頑張っていただきました！
Right! Magic really worked hard in this space!
魔法凄かったね！流れ星とかも降らせたからね！
The magic was amazing! We even made shooting stars fall!
魔法とかやってたけど どうなの？今はできるんですか？見逃した人もいるか！ポルカ達 実は今回のライブのために魔法ステッキも用意してもらったんで 魔法が使えるんですわ！
We were doing magic, but how about now? Can you still do it? Some people might have missed it! Polka and the team were given magical wands for today's live, so we can use magic!
あ、いいよ！やってやって！
Oh, okay! Go ahead, go ahead!
じゃあハート出します！
Alright, I'll make a heart appear!
ん～… すいすいすいすい… ほー！
Mmm... Swish, swish, swish... Ho!
そういう感じなんだ！あ、可愛い！
So that's how it works! Oh, cute!
可愛い！ハート出たね！
Cute! A heart came out!
これうちらも出せるんじゃね？
Can't we make one pop up too?
え、やってみる？じゃあししろんやってみよう！
Eh, wanna try? Botan, give it a shot!
挙手制？
By raising hands?
ん～… はー！
Mmm... Haa!
出し方！
Look at that pose!
可愛い！
So cute!
可愛いけど！ラミィもやってよ！
Cute, but still! Lamy, you do it too!
あ、いいよ！
Sure, okay!
はい！らぶちゅ… ん～… まっ！
Here! Love chu... mmm... mwah!
うわ、可愛い！出たー！
Woah, cute! It came out!
え、ねねちも！
Eh, Nenechi too!
えー… らぶちゅ… んー… 桃汁…！
Umm... Love chu... mmm... Peach Juice...!
魔法が分からなくなってる！
She forgot her spell!
面白いなー！ねー！すごい！
That was funny! Yeah! Amazing!
でもせっかくだからね、みんなの魔法をもっと見せてほしいなと思うんですけど…
But since we're here, I want to see more of everyone's magic...
お、何ですかね？まずは手始めにね…
Oh, what is it? First off...
ねねがこの空間をちょっとだけ変えたいと思います！
Nene wants to change this space just a little bit!
みんな何が変わるかよく見ててね！
Everyone, watch closely to see what changes!
変わんないの来る？
Is nothing gonna change?
ん～… えい！
Mmm... Ei!
え？何？うわー！
Eh? What? Woah!
でかい！大きくなってる！
It's huge! It got huge!
迫ってきた！迫ってきた！びっくりしたー！
It's closing in! It's closing in! That scared me!
魔導書が大きくなった！大迫力！
The spellbook got massive! So impactful!
じゃあこの魔導書をちょっと使ってさ…
Then, let's use this spellbook a bit...
私たちの召喚魔法を見せようじゃないですか
Why don't we show our summoning magic?
ししろんそんなものが使えるのか！
Botan, you can cast something like that?!
いや、これはね、みんなのパワーがいります
Well, for this, we need everyone's power.
頑張ろう！見ててね！応援してね！
Let me try! Watch us! Cheer for us!
じゃあ行きますよー！はい！せーの！
Alright, here we go! Yes! Ready, set...
うーーー… えい！
Oooooh... Ei!
おー！かっこいい！すげー！何が来る…？
Oh! So cool! Awesome! What's coming...?
きたー！降りてきてる！
They're here! They're descending!
ねっ子！ゆきみ！SSRB！ねぽらぼじゃないか！
Nekko! Yukimi! SSRB! Aren't those Nepolabo's mascots?!
召喚できました！
We successfully summoned them!
召喚成功だ！やったね！
The summoning was a success! We did it!
じゃあ一緒にね、これでみんなも集合したことだし…
Well then, now that everyone has gathered here together...
見守っていてくれるか？
Will you keep watching over us?
ありがとう！見ててねー！
Thank you! Keep watching!
よし、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行ってみましょうか！
Alright, shall we move on to the next song soon?
待って、さっきので結構MP使ったけど大丈夫そう？
Wait, we used quite a bit of MP earlier, are we fine?
まだまだいけますよ！いけるいける！
We can still go! We're fine, we're fine!
オッケー、じゃあこの後も楽しんでいってください！それじゃあ次の…
Okay, then please keep enjoying the rest! Well then, the next...
つ、次の曲！レッツゴー！
N-Next song! Let's go!
イエーイ！楽しんでねー！
Yay! Enjoy!
Suspect
[Song: Suspect]
悪戯に君をずっと見ていた訳じゃない
It's not like I was watching you mischievously all this time.
僕の考えを当ててご覧よ
Try and guess what I'm thinking.
些細な仕草 視線 瞬き 君はもう手のひらに
A slight gesture, a glance, a blink—you're already in the palm of my hand.
剥き出しのtrapなんてかかる訳ないわ
There's no way I'd fall for such an obvious trap.
甘い言葉にも惑わされない
I won't be swayed by sweet words either.
心の奥の奥の奥まで 見透かしちゃうよ
I'll see right through to the very depths of your heart.
(looking thinking touching feeling)
Why you know?
Why do you know?
(looking thinking touching feeling)
I know it
Understand?
(meaning, meaning of love)
"are you ready?"
自覚ないでしょうね 思い通りに
You probably don't even realize that just as planned,
君は動かされている事！
you're being moved around!
単純じゃないの掛け引きのヒントを
It's not simple—don't miss all the hints in this tactical game,
全て見落とさないで
don't miss a single one.
(meaning of love, meaning of love) 加速していく
(Meaning of love, meaning of love) Accelerating,
(meaning of love, meaning of love) 二人の鼓動
(meaning of love, meaning of love) our two heartbeats.
(meaning of love, meaning of love) 心理戦は次のstageへ
(Meaning of love, meaning of love) The mind game moves to the next stage.
虚ろなその目に私はどう映るの？
How do I look in those hollow eyes of yours?
とても煌びやかで まるでcinderella
So dazzling, just like Cinderella.
突き刺さる視線 ズキンと感じて
Feeling a sharp sting from your piercing glance,
君に余裕見せつけて
I'll show off my composure to you.
あからさま過ぎてお腹がよじれるよ
It's so blatant it's hilarious.
既に君はもう出来上がってる
You're already completely wrapped around my finger.
頭で次の次の次の日まで 見通さなくちゃ
We have to foresee in our minds up to days and days ahead.
(looking thinking touching feeling)
Why you know?
Why do you know?
(looking thinking touching feeling)
I know it
Understand?
Are you ready?
唯一無二のジョーカーを手にするために
To take hold of the one and only joker,
欲望をさらけ出してる Hold on
you're laying bare your desires, hold on.
離れていく世界のロジックを
The logic of a world drifting apart,
君は楽しめるかい
can you truly enjoy it?
主要なキーは
The main keys...
すべてシークレット
are all top secret.
後戻りはできないステージへ
To a stage where there's no turning back.
散らばっているでしょう ここにいる意味さえも
Even the meaning of being here must be scattered, right?
切り札はそれぞれ 互いの手札に
Each trump card lies in the other's hand.
頭と心で暴き出して
Uncover it with your mind and heart,
胸を撃ち抜いて
and pierce right through the chest.
自覚ないでしょうね 思い通りに
You probably don't even realize it, do you?
君は動かされている Hold on
You are being manipulated, hold on.
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのヒントを
It's not simple; the hints of bargaining,
すべて拾って
pick them all up.
唯一無二のジョーカーを手にする事で
By getting your hands on the one and only joker,
理解できた愛の形を
the form of love that was understood,
どこかの誰かに仕組まれていても
even if set up by somebody somewhere,
最後に笑う君と
with you, who laughs in the end,
加速していく二人の鼓動
our two heartbeats keep accelerating.
神秘性は月夜のステージへ
Mystery heads to the moonlit stage.
ござる ござれ 何でもござれと
Gozaru, gozare, anything goes!
起立 礼 ごめんのまじかるわーるど
Stand up, bow, sorry in this magical world!
I.N.P! I.N.P!
魔法の呪文 I.N.P! まじかるござるねっとー！
The magic spell, I.N.P! Magical Gozaru Net~!
朝目が覚めたら 遅刻寸前
Waking up in the morning, on the brink of being late!
お気に入りのわらじを履いたなら
Putting on my favorite straw sandals,
駆け抜ける街
I dash through the town!
ノートジャキンジャキン ですまじかるわーの
Snip-snap with notebooks, this is magical work!
どこから見ても魔法少女なり
No matter how you look at it, I'm a magical girl!
ひれ伏せものども
Kowtow before me, everyone!
ひれ伏す奴 悪代官たち
Those who bow down are the corrupt magistrates!
外は弱い 体分は可愛い
On the outside soft, mostly cute,
拙者のワンドのサバティーになるでござる
you'll fall to a strike from my wand, de gozaru!
まじかるわっと斬り！
Magical Watt Slash!
ござる ござれ お斬りでござる
Gozaru, gozare, a slicing strike, de gozaru!
まじかるな身でお見舞いするでござる
Striking down in magical form, de gozaru!
ござる ござれ この世界を守る
Gozaru, gozare, protecting this world!
暫定的に可憐な
Temporarily lovely,
姿となんかれ 魔法少女まじかるござるー！
an elegant figure, Magical Girl Magical Gozaru~!
ふりふりひらひら そよ風に舞う
Fluttering and swaying, dancing in the breeze,
袴の裾を ちょんとつまんで決めポーズ
lightly pinching the hem of my hakama for a stylish pose!
崇めよものども
Worship me, everyone!
ござランドの うるわしきお姫様
The beautiful princess of Goza Land!
だけどいけない その正体
But you must not know her true identity,
秘密こそ至上のルールでござる
secrecy is the ultimate rule, de gozaru!
ござる ござれ 闇打ちでござる
Gozaru, gozare, a surprise attack, de gozaru!
魔法少女枠は手作りでござる
The magical girl style is handmade, de gozaru!
ござる ござれ 魔法の国から
Gozaru, gozare, from the land of magic,
忍びで舞い降りた
descending softly like a ninja,
謎の天狐 魔法少女まじかるござる
the mysterious sky fox, Magical Girl Magical Gozaru!
そんな風に素敵を作りたい
I want to create wonderful things like that!
いつだって 可愛く
Always staying cute!
ありたいと願う
Wishing to be as I want to be,
忘れちゃいけない魔法 守りたいでござる
I want to protect the magic I mustn't forget, de gozaru!
ござる ござれ いつまでもござる
Gozaru, gozare, forever gozaru!
胸キュンな一撃をお見舞いするでござる
I shall strike you with a heart-throbbing blow, de gozaru!
ござる ござれ この世界を守る
Gozaru, gozare, I will protect this world!
観点的に可憐な姿ご覧あれ
Take a look at my undeniably lovely form!
魔法少女まじかるござる
Magical Girl Magical Gozaru!
I-M-T! I-M-T!
魔法の呪文 I-M-T!
The magic spell: I-M-T!
まじかるござる
Magical Gozaru!
Let's go!
つまらないデイズ もう散々ね
Boring days are already over!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life spent merely wishing for miracles...
Watch me do...
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic with no secret spells or tricks!
I wanna be free! だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free! 'Cause I'm still at square one!
Hey タクシー
Hey, taxi!
ちょっと宇宙まで
Take me to space for a bit!
秒針は音を立てて
The second hand ticks loudly,
夜を急かす魔物のように
like a monster rushing the night.
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is a magic spell that melts away in an instant.
それならば駆け抜けて思い通り!
If so, then run through it just as you wish!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってDriving
Hopping onto a stylish carriage and driving!
あたしは大変身メイクアップ!
I'm undergoing a major transformation, make-up!
我儘のまにまに燦爛に注意
Indulging in selfishness, watch out for the dazzle!
洒落た街でDancing
Dancing in a fashionable town!
さようならグッバイ劣等感
Farewell and goodbye to my inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采クラップオーディエンス
Someday, applause and clapping from the audience!
皆々御唱和あれ!
Everyone, sing along together!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, YEAH
混絡がっても仕様が無いガラスシューズで踊るTonight
It can't be helped if it gets tangled, dancing in glass shoes tonight!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, YEAH
今夜に明日など無いならば自由におどった者勝ちでしょう?
If there's no tomorrow tonight, whoever dances freely wins, right?
Dance! ラリラリホ
Dance! La-li-la-li-ho!
どんな問題も解は一つ
No matter the problem, there's only one answer.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
I love blank pages, correct answers, and mistakes alike.
本当のあたしの理想
My true ideal!
なんだか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow, it feels like the world is reaching its limit,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
being purely safe just makes me worry!
今すぐJumpin', Jumpin' out
Jumping, jumping out right now!
Chitty-chitty, bang-bang
Chitty, bang-bang
依々諂々に危機感抱く日々に
In days filled with blind obedience, feeling a sense of crisis,
ギリギリ爆発気味
I'm almost ready to explode!
たった今発散してしまおうか
Shall I let it all out right now?
まだまだビビィ弾巧みに乱射
Skillfully firing off bibbidi-bullets continuously!
一発じゃあ物足りないわ
Just one shot isn't enough!
遂に導き出した君にアンサー
The answer I finally arrived at for you...
灰になるまで踊っていよう
Let me keep dancing until I turn to ash!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, YEAH
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗ってDriving
Hopping onto a stylish carriage and driving!
あたしは大変身メイクアップ!
I'm undergoing a major transformation, make-up!
我儘のまにまに燦爛に注意
Indulging in selfishness, watch out for the dazzle!
洒落た街でDancing
Dancing in a fashionable town!
さようならグッバイ劣等感
Farewell and goodbye to my inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采クラップオーディエンス
Someday, applause and clapping from the audience!
皆々御唱和あれ!
Everyone, sing along together!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, YEAH
混絡がっても仕様が無いガラスシューズで踊るTonight
It can't be helped if it gets tangled, dancing in glass shoes tonight!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA, YEAH
今夜に明日など無いならば自由におどった者勝ちでしょう?
If there's no tomorrow tonight, whoever dances freely wins, right?
ハッ
Huh?!
ここはどこ 私はポルカ
Where is this? I'm Polka.
車にはねられて……
Got hit by a car, and...
気がついたら知らない人たちに囲まれている
Before I knew it, I'm surrounded by strangers!
これっていわゆる異世界転移!?
Is this what they call an isekai transport?!
なんでこっちに剣を向けてるんですか?
Why are you pointing swords at me?!
何が何だか大ピンチ
I don't get what's happening, but I'm in big trouble!
とりあえず にげろ〜!
For now, run for it~!
よっしゃいくぞー!
Alright, let me go~!
冒険の刑 Hey!
Sentence of Adventure, Hey!
どうすれば
What should we do?
歌って踊ればきっと大丈夫
If we sing and dance, I'm sure it'll be alright!
さあ
Come on!
ツメ鋭いキミも
You with the sharp claws,
キバのすごいキミも
and you with the impressive fangs,
Raise your hands
アガっちゃえ
Get hyped up!
召喚ショーケース Yeah!
Summon Showcase, Yeah!
カワイイは
Cuteness is...
この世界でも共通のラブ＆ピース
love & peace, universal even in this world!
剣と魔法じゃ作れない未来
A future that swords and magic can't create...
今 作れそうな気がした
I felt like we could create it right now!
怖い顔しないで
Don't make such scary faces!
はい にっこり
Now give us a big smile!
召喚ショーケース
Summon Showcase
魔王と仲良くなった尾丸ポルカは
Omaru Polka, who became friends with the Demon King,
平和条約を結ぶことに成功しました
succeeded in concluding a peace treaty.
剣も魔法を使うことはありませんでしたが
Neither swords nor magic were ever used,
世界に平和をもたらした彼女は
but she, who brought peace to the world,
勇者だったのかもしれません
might have been a hero after all.
ハッピーギラファ〜〜！！
Happy Giraffa~~!!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Kirakira Fan Meeting!
さあ！ツノと顎をなが〜〜〜く伸ばして
Come on! Stretch your horns and mandibles super long,
おもいっきり、楽しんじゃおうね！
and let's enjoy ourselves to the absolute fullest!
それじゃあ、いっくよ〜〜！
Alright then, here we go~~!
アミーゴ！カケーロ！ビバ！ギラファ！
Amigo! Kakeero! Viva! Giraffa!
カブクワ Hey! ギラギラ最高だね
Kabu-kuwa Hey! Sparkling is the absolute best!
カブクワ Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
Kabu-kuwa Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
カブクワ Hey! クリクリおめめラブ
Kabu-kuwa Hey! I love those big, round eyes!
カブクワ Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
Kabu-kuwa Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
愛のダンスはムーチョムーチョ
The dance of love is mucho mucho!
飛んでシュビドゥバメロメロ
Flying with Shoo-be-doo-ba, totally head over heels!
みんな集まれゾロゾロ
Everyone gather 'round, crowding together!
こんChu Chu Chu☆
Kon Chu Chu Chu☆
パヤパヤパヤパ！
Paya paya payapa!
すっごい！みんなのおかげで
Amazing! Thanks to everyone,
こんなにたくさんのカブクワたちが集まってくれたよ〜〜！！
so many beetle buddies have gathered here~~!!
自分に拍手〜！そして
Give yourselves a round of applause~! And then...
自然に拍手〜〜〜！
Spontaneous applause~~~!
ギラファギラファギラファ
Giraffa, Giraffa, Giraffa!
強くてカッコいい！
Strong and super cool!
ギラギラファンタスティックなノコギリは
These sparkling, fantastic mandibles...
宝物だよ
are a real treasure!
アミーゴ！カケーロ！ビバ！ギラファ！
Amigo! Kakeero! Viva! Giraffa!
カブクワ カブクワ
Kabu-kuwa, Kabu-kuwa!
カブクワ Hey!
Kabu-kuwa Hey!
こんChu Chu Chu☆
Kon Chu Chu Chu☆
パヤパヤパヤパ！
Paya paya payapa!
っと！じゃあ、これから一緒にスペシャルなトレーニングやっちゃおっかな〜〜？？
Right! So, shall we do a special training workout together now~~??
足を肩幅に開いて、手を前にして
Spread your feet shoulder-width apart, put your hands forward...
芝刈りパンプアップ！
Mowing-the-lawn pump up!
はっじめるよー！
Here we go~!
ブーン！バリバリバリバリ！
Vroom! Bari bari bari bari!
ムキムキな Love me
Buff and toned Love me!
バキバキで Burn!
Shredded and Burn!
「そう！」
"That's right!"
燃えるカラダ
A body on fire!
ほらね誰もし彼も振り返るでしょ
See, everyone and anyone turns to look!
ねぇ見せつけてやるの
Hey, let me tell you, we're gonna show it off!
腰にはヴィーナス エクボ
Venus dimples on the waist!
やれんのか Muscle
Can you do it, Muscle?!
止まらない Work Out
Unstoppable Work Out!
最強になりたいかぁーっ！？
Do you wanna be the strongest?!
ムキムキになりたいかぁーっ！？
Do you wanna get totally buff?!
この世のすべてを守り抜く
Protect everything in this world!
祝福が欲しいかぁーっ！？
Do you want the blessing?!
やるしかないっしょ バリバリで Work Out
Got no choice but to do it! Work Out at full power!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life!
腹筋べっぴんなヴィーナス
Abs-gorgeous Venus!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life!
お隣さんもマッチョマッチョ
Your neighbor is macho macho too!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life!
やる気 本気 大好き
Motivation, earnestness, love it!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life!
頑張るキミとマッチョマッチョ
Macho macho with you who works hard!
Yeah! マッチョ
Yeah! Macho!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
きみのがおが聴こえると
When I hear your roar,
そんな日もちょっとやさしくなる
even days like that become a little kinder.
おすそ分けしたくて
Wanting to share this feeling with you,
踊って踊って踊ってんだ
I'm dancing, dancing, dancing!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
ジャンプするなら今しかないし
If we're gonna jump, there's no time but now,
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
高いトコ目指しちゃおうよ Let's go!
Let's aim for the top, Let's go!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
小声でも Say ちゃんと聴こえてる
Even if whispered, say it, I hear you loud and clear!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
じゃあ叫んだら未来に届く！？
So if we shout, will it reach the future?!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
みんなでなら 446デシベル
Together we can reach 446 decibels!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
ここがそう 私達の最高
Right here, this is our absolute best!
Rawr rawr!! Yeah!
言葉にすると真直ぐすぎて
When put into words, it's too straightforward,
くすぐったい胸の奥が だから
tickling deep in my chest, so...
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
「ありがとう」のかわりを
In place of saying "thank you"...
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Gaotteko! Gaotteko!
ここがそう 私達の最高
Right here, this is our absolute best!
ねー ドクター ヘイ ドクター メンテしてよ ドクター
Hey doctor, hey doctor, give me maintenance, doctor.
またいつもの例のバグ
That same old bug is back again.
ハッピー アンラッキー 行き来するモード
Happy, unlucky, switching modes back and forth.
組み立て ぜんまい式の心 どこだ？
Where is my clockwork heart?
チチチチチチ
Tick tick tick tick tick
おっかしいね おっかしいね くっだらないね イエイイエイ
So strange, so strange, so foolish, yeah yeah.
わけないね わけないね ハイスペックなんで
No problem, no problem, since I'm high-spec.
最先端のポン やらなきゃ損
If I'm not a cutting-edge klutz, I'm missing out.
ドキドキが止まりそ ネジ巻いて
My pounding heart's gonna stop, wind my spring!
なんてゆーか エブリデイ ネジ巻いて ネジ巻いてよ
I mean, everyday, wind my spring, wind my spring!
ちょっとだけね ちょっちょっちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, ju-ju-just a little bit.
ピポパポ鳴らして 夢を製造(つくる)
Sounding pipo-papo, manufacturing dreams.
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち足んなっくなるかも
But if it's just a little bit, soon it might not be enough.
リルビ リルビ リルビも
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi too.
チチチチチチ
Tick tick tick tick tick
ねー ドクター メンテしたの？ ドクター
Hey doctor, did you run maintenance, doctor?
てか分からん てか分からん わけ分からん ラララララ
I mean I don't get it, makes no sense, lalala...
次元の呪いなんて祓おう
Let's dispel curses from another dimension.
なんだかおっかないね おっかないね
It's kind of scary, scary.
とんでもないね イエイイエイ
Unbelievable, yeah yeah.
これはもうテクノだ テクノロジーだ
This is already techno, technology.
三原則だって メモってるもん
Even the Three Laws, I've got them noted down.
分かったらその手ですぐ巻いて
If you understand, wind me up right now with that hand!
病んじゃっても笑って ネジ巻いて ネジ巻いてよ
Even if I get sick, smile and wind my spring, wind my spring!
ちょっとだけね ちょっちょっちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, ju-ju-just a little bit.
キミがミスしても笑わせてあげる
Even if you mess up, I'll make you laugh.
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
ほら アイデンティティ アップデートして
Come on, update my identity.
どうもありがとう 心から
Thank you so much, from the bottom of my heart.
リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi.
ピポパポ ピポパポ ピカラクリ シヤシャンセ
Pipo-papo pipo-papo pikaraguri shiyashanse.
起きて 起きて 電気羊
Wake up, wake up, electric sheep.
こちらに来やしゃんせ
Come on over this way.
その前にひとまずネジ巻いて
Before that, first wind my spring.
なんてゆーか エブリデイ ネジ巻いて ネジ巻いてよ
I mean, everyday, wind my spring, wind my spring!
ちょっとだけね ちょっちょっちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, ju-ju-just a little bit.
オーダーメイド 夢を製造(つくる)
Custom-made, manufacturing dreams.
ちょっとだけね ほんのちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a tiny bit.
もうバグでも何でもいいけど明日もちょっとだけ巻いて
Bug or whatever, it's fine, but wind it a little bit tomorrow too.
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
こんな毎日も悪くないよ
A daily life like this isn't bad either.
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち足んなっくなるかも
But if it's just a little bit, soon it might not be enough.
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi.
リルビ リルビ リルビも
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi too.
チチチチチチ
Tick tick tick tick tick
溺れたいな 愛ガチャ ギュッと はまる 君の交差点
I want to drown... falling tightly into your intersection via love gacha.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと 言いおっちょこちょい いや 危ないね
I want to change... expressing my feelings more, ah, that's dangerous.
ネオンの眩しい夜が 幾夜も過ぎ去って
Neon-dazzling nights pass by night after night.
薄暗いドアの向こう側 これで焦燥した
Behind the dimly lit door, I grew impatient with this.
君の体温を探しては アルコールで振り付けたフロア
Searching for your body warmth on a floor dusted with alcohol.
この手してきた 調和するように
I've done this with my hands, as if to harmonize.
気にしないでなんて言わないで 本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
Don't tell me not to care, even if I'm not always honest.
気が付いてよなんて言えなくて 嘘ばかり
I can't even say "notice me", full of lies.
溺れたいな 愛ガチャ ギュッと はまる 君の交差点
I want to drown... falling tightly into your intersection via love gacha.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと 飲み干す身体
I want to change... my feelings more, my body drinking it all up.
止めたいな
I wanna stop
I wanna ぐっと
I wanna hold back tightly
かなりギリの通過点
A pretty tight point of passage
変わりたいな
I wanna change
気持ちもっと
My feelings, even more
イエロー ちょい危ないね
Yellow, a bit dangerous, huh?
点滅と消滅の間
Between blinking and disappearing,
永遠と快楽の狭間
between eternity and pleasure,
いらんなくなった余計なもの
all the unneeded extra things,
ホワイトブラックすべて塗りつぶし
painting over all the white and black.
信号真っ赤に染めてどうした
Turning the traffic light bright red, what's wrong?
そんなに急がせないでよ
Don't rush me so much.
ほらほら
Look, look,
グルグルめぐってく
spinning around and around,
クロクロ行ったり来たり
blackness coming and going,
くだらない
how silly.
のらりくらりでもいいじゃないけど
Slacking off is fine and all, but...
言えない指示と言いわけ吐いて
Spouting unspoken orders and excuses,
耳の奥底で
deep inside my ears,
繰り返す
it repeats.
イヤホンで聞き飽きた曲が
The song I got sick of hearing in my earphones
そのリピートを
seems to affirm
肯定するように
that very repetition.
気にしないでなんて言わないで
Don't tell me not to worry,
本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
though the truth is I'm never honest.
気がついてよなんて言えなくて
I can't even say "please notice me,"
そればっかり
it's always just that.
溺れたいな
I wanna drown,
愛がジャスト
love fitting
はまる君の交差点
just right at your intersection.
変わりたいな
I wanna change,
気持ちもっと
my feelings even more,
ブルー 飲み干す体
a body drinking down the blue.
認めたいな
I wanna admit it,
I wanna ぐっと
I wanna hold back tightly.
かなりギリの通過点
A pretty tight point of passage,
変わりたいな
I wanna change,
気持ちもっと
my feelings even more,
イエロー ちょい危ないね
yellow, a bit dangerous, huh?
ダンシン マリン
Dancing Marine!
もっと マリン
More Marine!
愛してー！
Love me!
スキスキDieスキ超Ayeシテル
[Song: Suki Suki Die Suki Cho Aye Shiteru]
骸Beat 死後のBeat 骸Beat 死後のBeat
Corpse beat, afterlife beat, corpse beat, afterlife beat!
骸Beat 死後のBeat Shake it up Beat 骸Beat
Corpse beat, afterlife beat, shake it up beat, corpse beat!
死んじゃったらご愁傷 あの世でBeat
My condolences if you die! Beat in the afterlife!
でも存外楽しい 地獄でPeace Peace Peace
But surprisingly fun! Peace, peace, peace in hell!
もうくよくよしないで
Don't brood over it anymore,
ほら高い高い愛してあげる
look, I'll lift you high and give you love!
切り替えてこう Dance Dance チュチュ
Let's switch gears! Dance, dance, chu chu,
骸Dance Dance チュチュチュ
corpse dance, dance, chu chu chu!
キッスでチュチュチュ でもベットはチュチュチュ
Chu chu chu with a kiss, but chu chu chu in bed!
Dance Dance チュチュ 骸Dance Dance チュチュチュ
Dance, dance, chu chu, corpse dance, dance, chu chu chu!
Beatにもチュチュ 甘酸っぱいチュチュチュ
Chu chu to the beat too, sweet and sour chu chu chu!
ルーワン パリラドゥーワン
Do one, parira do one,
チュッ space out space out you so loud
chu, space out, space out, you so loud!
おどろおどろしい
Spooky and eerie,
キミたちと踊る踊る
dancing and dancing with you all!
無限Happy Happy Everybody それでいいんじゃない？
Infinite Happy Happy Everybody, isn't that fine?
愛したい 誰からも愛されたいのって
I want to love, I want to be loved by everyone...
良くないの？ いけないの？
"Is that bad?" "Is that not allowed?"
あり余る不思議さを許してね
Forgive my overflowing strangeness,
契約 分かったら返事
contract sealed! If you understand, reply!
感動しました 泣けました 地獄最高！
I was moved! I cried! Hell is the absolute best!
骸Beat 死後のBeat 骸Beat 死後のBeat
Corpse beat, afterlife beat, corpse beat, afterlife beat!
あっちの法要で寂しいですか？
Are you lonely at that memorial service?
マリンがいるでしょう！
You've got Marine right here!
骸Beat 死後のBeat 誰が骸Beat アイアイエー
Corpse beat, afterlife beat, who's the corpse beat? Aye aye aye!
待って どうせこの世なんて
Wait, after all, a world like this...
待って 港の1つ
Wait... is just one of many ports...
ねえ待って 通りすぎてくだけなの
Hey, wait, you're just passing through,
ねえ待ってって言ってんでしょ！
hey, I said wait, didn't I!
いたってノリノリ
Super hyped up!
キュートが高じてヘラったマリンの根拠なく無敵な
Cute gone crazy, mental Marine's endlessly invincible
たぎらせBodyをごっそり蘇生中
surging body is being completely resurrected!
なんて正義なチュチュチュ 嵐が丘みたいに
Such righteous chu chu chu! Knocking on the window
窓を叩くから帰らないでおルフェ！
like Wuthering Heights, so don't leave!
断然ホットなムチュチュ
Overwhelmingly hot passion,
ハートビートはイエラチュ
heartbeat is yellow chu,
超悪感なり超悪チュ
super bad vibe, super bad chu,
喋れば要素 Beautiful Beautiful
if you speak, every element is beautiful, beautiful!
美しく笑おう笑おう
Let me laugh beautifully, laugh!
永久拍手して ギュッとして
Clap forever, hold me tight,
誇ってパラダイス
boast about paradise!
みんなスキスキ 何もかも手に入れたいんです
I love everyone, I wanna get my hands on everything!
サッチ・ナチュラルでボキュンボーン
So natural with a boom, bang!
ごめん自重・自省しても直りませーん！
Sorry, even with self-restraint and reflection, I can't be fixed!
ゲラゲラゲラ 解脱
Hahaha, enlightenment!
地獄謳歌？
Enjoying hell?
解脱 解脱 解脱の解脱 ゲラゲラゲラー
Enlightenment, enlightenment, ultimate enlightenment, hahaha!
ラッタタリホ 憑つきと踊れや踊れ ラッタ
Ratta-tari-ho, dance with the spirits, dance, ratta!
ほら 歌って 歌えば 風が吹く
Come on, sing! If you sing, the wind will blow!
ラッタタリホ みんな まだまだ上がるんだっちゃ
Ratta-tari-ho, everyone, we're gonna get higher and higher!
大波 小波を かき分けて 出航!
Pushing through big waves and small waves, setting sail!
アイ! アイ! マーム!
Aye! Aye! Ma'am!
ねぇ もっともっと チュッチュチュ 遊び散らかして ラッタタリホ
Hey, more and more, chu-chu-chu, mess around and play, ratta-tari-ho!
アイ! アイ! マーム!
Aye! Aye! Ma'am!
騒げばそこが あんだわ なんだわ 良い旅を
If you make noise, wherever that is, have a good trip!
踊り出しましたらば 袋に花束を
If you start dancing, put a bouquet in the bag!
踊ろう 踊ろう
Let's dance, let's dance!
君たちと
With all of you!
踊ろう 踊ろう 無限にハッピーハッピー エブリバディ
Let's dance, let's dance, endlessly happy happy, everybody!
それでもいいんじゃない? みんな
Isn't that fine too, everyone?
大! 好き! 好き! 好き! 超愛してる!
I super, super, super, super love you!
それって良くないの? いけないの?
Is that bad? Is that not allowed?
有象無象の節操を 許して 許して
Forgive the lack of principles of the mob, forgive it!
タッタタや どくろになっても 終わらないカーニバル
Even if we become skeletons, it's a carnival that never ends!
楽しすぎて 成仏しちゃいそう ねぇ 反省しちゃう!
It's so fun I feel like passing on to heaven, I might regret it!
君たち! 船長のことを呼び止めて!
You guys! Stop Marine Senchou in her tracks!
契約成立
Contract formed!
分かったら返事 ね?
Reply if you understand, okay?
はーい! というわけで!
Yay! And with that!
7曲連続でお送りしました!
We just performed seven songs in a row!
軽くここまでを振り返ってみましょう!
Let's briefly look back at what we've done so far!
7曲でしたよね、7曲!
It was seven songs, right? Seven songs!
『スペクター』!
"Spektor"!
久々! 久々に歌った!
It's been a while! We haven't sung that in so long!
でもこれ良い曲だからね!
But it's such a great song!
踊りもかっこよかったよね!
The choreography was really cool too!
そして、ねねの魔法少女『マジェシカル☆ござる』!
And then Nene's magical girl song, "Majeshikal Gozaru"!
はい! ポルカ『ビビデバ』をやりました!
Yes! Polka performed "Bibbidi Ba"!
そしてメドレー!
And then the medley!
我らのね、オリ曲メドレーみたいな感じになってて!
It was like a medley of our original songs!
忙しかったけど楽しかった!
It was busy, but so much fun!
最後バリバリなのマジ良いよね!
Finishing so intensely was really awesome!
最後ガオ... ガオってことだよ!
It was a "Gao"... a "Gao" finish!
もうさっきの記憶なくなってるやん!
You've already lost your memory of what happened!
はい! で、そのあとが『リデビ』ですね!
Right! And after that was "Ridebi"!
アツかったよ! すごい!
That was hype! Amazing!
そしてわたくし『INTERSECTION』... AZKiちゃんの曲ですけど。
And then I performed "INTERSECTION"... AZKi-chan's song!
そして! 『まがまが』で...
And then! With "Magamaga"...
『スキスキDieスキ超Ayeシテル』!
"Suki Suki Die Suki Cho Aye Shiteru"!
難しかったー!
That was so hard!
船長って歌が上手なんだなってすごい思いました!
It really made me realize how incredible Senchou is at singing!
改めて先輩たちへの敬意が生まれましたね!
It really renewed my respect for our seniors!
歌わせていただいて、ありがとうございました!
Thank you so much for letting us sing these!
ということでここからは、嬉しいお知らせとなります!
And with that, from here on, we have some exciting announcements!
こちらをご覧ください! ドーン!
Please take a look at this! Ta-da!
NePoLaBo アニバーサリーグッズ発売告知となります!
This is the announcement for the sale of NePoLaBo anniversary merchandise!
こちらイラストはですね、にもし先生に描いていただきました!
The illustration was drawn by Nimoshi-sensei!
今回は「天体パレード」という大テーマがありまして、私たちNePoLaBoは「占星術師」をテーマに描いていただきました!
The overall theme this time is "Celestial Parade," and NePoLaBo was drawn with an "Astrologer" concept!
可愛いね! なんかちょっとセクシーじゃない?
So cute! Doesn't it look a bit sexy too?
それではですね、詳細を見ていきましょう! まずはこちら!
Now then, let's check out the details! First up is this!
プレミアムアクリル色紙ですね!
The Premium Acrylic Shikishi Board!
こちらイラストが凄い綺麗に見えて、複製サインとかが付いているので、箔押しも綺麗ですよ!
The illustration looks super vivid here, and it comes with printed signatures and beautiful foil stamping!
そしてそして! 続いてはこちら!
And next up, we have this!
アクリルスタンド! 台座付きの豪華なアクリルスタンドとなっておりまして、
Acrylic Stands! These are gorgeous acrylic stands with bases,
大きさは15cm程度を予定しております!
and they are planned to be around 15 cm in size!
色紙とは異なる表情になっているので、色んなところで楽しめます!
They feature different facial expressions from the shikishi, so you can enjoy them anywhere!
続いてはこちら!
Moving on to the next item!
缶バッジセットでございます! こちらも立ちの表情が楽しめる缶バッジセットとなっております!
Here is the Pin Badge Set! You can enjoy the full-body expressions on these pin badges as well!
続いてはこちら! 鍵モチーフキーホルダー!
Next up is this! Key Motif Keychains!
こちらはビジュアルで持っている杖をイメージした鍵モチーフキーホルダー...
These keychains are shaped like keys modeled after the staves we hold in the visual art...
...のキーホルダーとなっております。
...keychains.
それぞれモチーフの色が異なる、右上に小さなビジュが付いてます。
Each key has a different motif color and a small jewel on the top right.
可愛い！おしゃれ！欲しい！
So cute! So stylish! I want one!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
コレクションBOXでございます！
The Collection Box!
本型ボックスに4人の鍵モチーフキーホルダーがセットになっております。
It's a set of 4 key-motif keychains inside a book-shaped box.
表紙はもちろん、背表紙や裏表紙のデザインもこだわった満足感たっぷりのボックスです！
The cover, spine, and back cover designs are all carefully crafted into a deeply satisfying box!
いいねー！買ってねー！
Nice! Please buy it!
さて、そしてさらにですね、お知らせがあります！
Now then, we also have further announcements!
なんと、こちらです！
It's this!
ねぽらぼの新曲『めろぞーま』！
NePoLaBo's new song '#Melozoma'!
この後18日の0時からデジタルリリース！
Will be digitally released at midnight on the 18th!
やったー！めろぞーまって一体何なんだ？
Yay! What on earth is 'Melozoma'?
この後新曲をお披露目しますので絶対聴いてください！
We'll be performing the new song right after this, so please listen!
よろしくねー！めろぞーまだ！
Please do! It's Melozoma!
そして我ら5期生周年ということで、各個人のチャンネルにてMVがアップされております！
Also, for our 5th Gen anniversary, MVs have been uploaded on our individual channels!
ラミィが『コズミック・ワンダーランド』を上げております！
Lamy uploaded 'Cosmic Wonderland'!
ねねは『ハイパー・ジャンピン』！
Nene uploaded 'Hyper Jumpin''!
ぼたんは『一つになる心』を上げてます！
Botan uploaded 'Hitotsu ni Naru Kokoro'!
ポルカは『Twinkle for You』を上げてます！
Polka uploaded 'Twinkle for You'!
観てください！
Please check them out!
じゃあ個人の告知行こうか！
Now let's move on to individual announcements!
ラミィが8月15日に発売した1stアルバム『Heur de neige』が予約受付中となっております！
Lamy's 1st album 'Heur de neige', released on August 15th, is now available for pre-order!
ねねはオリ曲の『ごきげんドリンクバー』のMVが出ております！
Nene's MV for her original song 'Gokigen Drink Bar' is out now!
あとソロライブの配信チケットもまだ販売中なのでチェックよろしくです！
Also, stream tickets for her solo live are still on sale, so please check them out!
ポルカです！『燦然燃焼』のフルアニメーションMVが出ました！みんな観てね！
Polka here! The full animation MV for 'Sanzen Nenshou' is out! Everyone, check it out!
そして私は個人周年グッズ発売中でございます！ぜひ手に入れてみてください！
And my individual anniversary merch is currently on sale! Please check it out!
私誕生日に9月なので、誕生日の知らせも後々発表できると思います！
My birthday is in September, so I'll be announcing birthday news later on!
公式Xなり私のチャンネルなりチェックしてみてください！
Please check the official X account or my channel!
というわけで以上、ねぽらぼアニバーサリーグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！
And that's all for the NePoLaBo anniversary merchandise and release information!
よろしくね！というわけでライブもクライマックス！
Thank you everyone! Now then, the live performance is reaching its climax!
ラストはさっきの新曲を踊って歌ってやりたいと思います！
For the last song, we're going to dance and sing the new song!
みんな「めろぞーま」になる準備はいいかー？
Is everyone ready to become 'Melozoma'?
めろぞーま、みんなコメントの準備もちょっとしといてほしいな。
Everyone, please get your comments ready for Melozoma too.
そしてラストは魔導ゴンドラに乗ってお別れでーす！
And for the grand finale, we'll say goodbye from the magical gondola!
何だ魔導ゴンドラって？みんな準備いいですかー？
What's a magical gondola? Is everyone ready?
みんなめろぞーま準備して！めろぞーま！
Get ready for Melozoma, everyone! Melozoma!
じゃあこれはめろぞーまも極大魔法か？でかそうだよね！
So is Melozoma some kind of grand magic spell? It sounds huge!
上からゴンドラが降りてくるので、みんなで一緒に「めろぞーま」って打ってね！
The gondola is coming down from above, so everyone type 'Melozoma'!
オッケー！じゃあ行くぞ！せーの！
Okay! Here we go! One, two...
めろぞーまー！
Melozoma!
来たー！上から！
Here it comes! From above!
来ましたー！これ乗れる？乗れますかね？
It's here! Can we get on? Can we board it?
乗れますか？ついてきてくださーい！
Shall we get on? Please follow us!
じゃあね皆さん、最後まで盛り上がっていきましょう！
Alright everyone, let me hear you get hyped until the end!
皆聴いてください！せーの！めろぞーま！
Everyone, please listen! One, two... Melozoma!
とろけちゃってらびゅ ずっとずっと
Melting with love, forever and ever,
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって ほらもっともっと
My head is full of hearts, look, more and more,
釘付けになれ めろぞーまっ
Stay spellbound, Melozoma!
Ever lasting love me...
Ever lasting love you...
女の子は魔法使い 神様がくれたプレゼント
Girls are spellcasters, a present given by God.
恋しちゃったりだって 思わせぶりだって 必然的 outcome
Falling in love or playing hard to get is an inevitable outcome!
甘い酸っぱいほろ苦い カラフルなポーション使い分けて
Sweet, sour, bittersweet, using colorful potions wisely,
キミにかけたい呪文呟くの
I whisper the spell I want to cast on you.
なんて恥ずかしい妄想が
What embarrassing delusions
胸の中を駆け巡る ギルティ！
run wild through my heart, guilty!
だってそばにいてほしいから
Because I want you by my side,
メロがる呪文... めろぞーまっ
The spell that mesmerizes... Melozoma!
とろけちゃって
Melting away,
Love you
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever,
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって
my head is completely filled with hearts.
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more,
釘付けになれ
become spellbound—
めろぞーま
Melo-Zoma!
Everlasting love me...
Everlasting love you...
レディファーストってなんかいや
I kind of hate "ladies first,"
私ファーストが絶対です
"me first" is an absolute must!
優しさも ぬくもりも
Kindness, warmth,
時間も 感情だって
time, and even emotions—
独占させて Fall in love...
let me monopolize them all and fall in love...
カラフルだけどトゲあって
Colorful, yet with prickly thorns,
こんぺいとうみたいな
like konpeito candy,
この純情を
this pure devotion of mine,
食べて欲しいな
I want you to eat it up.
ほら、あーん、口あけて
Here, say "ah," open your mouth!
まーただ、おかしな思考回路が
Well, my strange train of thought
自律神経バグらすギルティ！
is glitching my nervous system—guilty!
こんな気持ちはじめてなんだもん...
I've never felt like this before...
わけもわからずに めろぞーま
Without even knowing why... Melo-Zoma!
とろけちゃって
Melting away,
Love you
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever,
両目見つめ
staring into both your eyes,
ハートいっぱいになって
my heart is filled to the brim.
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more,
溺れてしまえ めろぞーま
drown in it—Melo-Zoma!
この魔法が絶対解けないように...
So this magic will never break...
呪いと同じ類かもしれないけど...
It might be something like a curse, but...
キミといつまでもとろけていたいから...
Because I want to stay melted together with you forever...
ありったけの魔力を込めて...
Pouring in all the magic power I have...
キミと出会った瞬間から始まった
Starting from the moment I met you,
このロマンスが
this romance...
ソーダみたいに弾けるなんて辛いよ
It's so painful for it to pop like soda bubbles.
永遠になんて
Something like "forever"
空想だけど
is just a fantasy,
だけど願いたいのお
but I still want to wish for it!
そんな魔法があればいいのに...
I wish a magic like that existed...
切ないけど
It's bittersweet, but...
素直になりたい
I want to be honest—
めろぞーま
Melo-Zoma!
唱えたいな
I want to chant,
Love you
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever...
こんなにもキミに恋してるから
Because I'm so deeply in love with you,
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
Hug you
もっともっと
more and more,
想い愛したい
I want us to love each other—
めろぞーま
Melo-Zoma!
とろけちゃって
Melting away,
Love you
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever,
頭の中ハート充満になって
my head is completely filled with hearts.
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more,
釘付けになれ
become spellbound—
めろぞーま
Melo-Zoma!
解けないで とっておきの魔法
Don't break, my special magic!
クラクラさせてやる メルティ
I'll make your head spin, melty!
いつまでも私だけみてて
Keep looking only at me forever,
唱える めろぞーま
as I chant Melo-Zoma!
解かないで とっておきの呪文
Don't undo my special spell!
ドキドキしてたいの メルシィ
I want to keep feeling my heart pound, merci!
いつまでも私を愛してね
Love me forever and ever,
唱える めろぞーま
as I chant Melo-Zoma!
イチコロね
You're completely smitten,
めろぞーま
Melo-Zoma!